const dayThirteenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) was born in the month of Rabi’ul Awwal and died in the month of …………",
    options: ["Muharam", "Ramadan", "Rabi’ul Awwal", "Safar", "Shawwal"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first new born baby in Islam after Hijrah (migration to Madinah)?",
    options: [
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "Anas bn Malik",
      "‘Abdullahi bn ‘Umar",
      "‘Abdullah bn Zubayr bn ‘Awam",
      "‘Abdullahi bn Abbas",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who (among the companions) was nicknamed Saifullahil maslul?",
    options: [
      "Hamza bn ‘Abdil Mutallib",
      "Khalid bn Walid",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who are ‘Abaadillah (four ‘Abdullah among the companions)?",
    options: [
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Amr, ‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas, ‘Abdullah bn Mas’ud and ‘Abdullah bn Zubayr",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Umar, ‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas, ‘Abdullah bn Mas’ud and ‘Abdullah bn Zubayr",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Umar, ‘Abdullah bn ‘Za’d, ‘Abdullah bn Mas’ud and ‘Abdullah bn Zubayr",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Umar, ‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas, ‘Abdullah bn Mas’ud and ‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Umar, ‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas, ‘Abdullah bn Uthman and ‘Abdullah bn Zubayr",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the real name of Abu Dajaanah (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "Uthman bn ‘Amr",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Muslim Ambassador in the history of Islam?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "Uthman bn ‘Amr",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was nicknamed Sayyid Shuadai (Master of Martyrs) among the companions?",
    options: [
      "Hamza bn ‘Abdul Mutallib",
      "Khalid bn Walid",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the real name of Abubakr Siddiq (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "‘Uthman bn ‘Umar",
      "‘Abdullah bn Maslul",
      "Sadiq bn Mas’ud",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Atiq",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was nicknamed Asadullah wa asadu rosuul (Allah and His messenger’s lion)?",
    options: [
      "Hamza bn ‘Abdil Mutallib",
      "Khalid bn Walid",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "In which month was the battle of Badr fought?",
    options: ["Muharam", "Ramadan", "Rabi’ul Awwal", "Safar", "Shawwal"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Female Martyr in Islam?",
    options: [
      "Ummu Sulaim",
      "Asmau bint Abibakr",
      "Sumyyah Ummu ‘Ammar bn Yasir",
      "Khadijat bint Khuwailid",
      "Khaolah bint Tha’labah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where did Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) used to gather his companions in Mecca to tell them the new revelation? In the house of ……",
    options: [
      "Abubakr Sidiq",
      "Arqam bn Abi Arqam",
      "Abi Talib",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
      "Zayd bn Abi Waqas",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the companion that was absent during battle of Badr due to sickness of his wife and the Prophet confirmed it that he has the reward like those that participated at the battle of Badr?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "‘Uthman bn ‘Affan",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who stabbed Umar bn Khatab (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "Abu Luhluati Almajusiy",
      "‘Abdullahi bn Maslul",
      "Ubayi bn Khalaf",
      "Ja’sh bn Ubal",
      "‘Abdur Rahman bn Muljama",
      "Wahsha bn ‘Aas",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was Saibul sirin-nabiy (companion in charge of confidential information)?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "‘Abdullah bn Abi Quhafa",
      "Uthman bn ‘Amr",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];

export default dayThirteenQuestions;
